<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Contours of Consciousness</title>
        <link>https://thesecretobserver7.github.io/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Contours of Consciousness</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 16:04:18 &#43;0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thesecretobserver7.github.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>The Value of Life: A Heartfelt Lesson from My Recent Visit Back Home</title>
    <link>https://thesecretobserver7.github.io/value-of-life/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 16:04:18 &#43;0900</pubDate>
    <author>TheSecretObserver</author>
    <guid>https://thesecretobserver7.github.io/value-of-life/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[My Beloved Country (Copyright © [2024] [TheSecretObserver])
It’s been a while since I last wrote… I recently returned home after two and a half years, and the experience was nothing short of surreal. But today, I want to share something that really touched me during my trip—something that shook me to my core, something that made me weep inside. It was one of those moments that broke something inside me, something I didn’t even realize needed breaking.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Saying Goodbye to My Favorite Shoes: A Journey of Comfort and Memories</title>
    <link>https://thesecretobserver7.github.io/my-shoes/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 22:26:39 &#43;0900</pubDate>
    <author>TheSecretObserver</author>
    <guid>https://thesecretobserver7.github.io/my-shoes/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[My Beloved FILA (Copyright © [2023] [TheSecretObserver])
Hey there, it&rsquo;s been a while since I last sat down to write. Today, I want to share a story that&rsquo;s close to my heart—it&rsquo;s about a pair of shoes that have been with me through thick and thin.
I remember buying these shoes back in December 2019, about six months after I moved to a new country. A friend helped me pick them out, saying they suited me perfectly.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Rediscovering Serenity: A Journey Back to Nature</title>
    <link>https://thesecretobserver7.github.io/okutama-hiking/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 18:22:21 &#43;0900</pubDate>
    <author>TheSecretObserver</author>
    <guid>https://thesecretobserver7.github.io/okutama-hiking/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[_Green Hills and River Bliss_ Location: [Okutama, Tokyo, Japan], Date: [Oct 08, 2023] (Copyright © [2023] [TheSecretObserver]) When Tokyo comes to mind, we usually think of a bustling city with tall buildings and bright lights. But there&rsquo;s a hidden treasure within Tokyo, a place surrounded by clear blue waters and beautiful hills - Okutama. It&rsquo;s in the western part of Tokyo, about 60 kilometers away from the busy city center.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>The Beginning: My Journey as &#34;The Secret Observer&#34;</title>
    <link>https://thesecretobserver7.github.io/hello_world/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 00:36:29 &#43;0900</pubDate>
    <author>TheSecretObserver</author>
    <guid>https://thesecretobserver7.github.io/hello_world/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Endless Ocean Among the Clouds Location: [Mt. Yahiko, Niigata, Japan], Date: [Feb 24, 2023] (Copyright © [2023] [TheSecretObserver])
I've had the desire to create an online blog for nearly a decade now. It's been a persistent dream of mine, a place where I can pour out my musings online. While I've been keeping daily journals over the years, sharing my inner thoughts on the internet feels like an entirely different challenge.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
